tabletopgamer.com 2011-11-10

# Privacy Policy | TabletopGamer.com

You are here: [Home](http://www.tabletopgamer.com/) / Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY:**

TabletopGamer.com, operated by Ignite Vision Marketing Inc.., has created this statement of privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy by informing visitors to our site as to the uses we make of the information they provide to us. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: TABLETOPGAMER.COM.

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to help identify you, to provide access to certain content, and to gather broad demographic information.

Our site’s registration forms may require users to give us contact information (such as name and email address) and financial information (such as account or credit card numbers) “Information”. You authorize this Information to be used by us in order to complete any transactions, receive any promotional material or to contact you when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to check the users’ qualifications for registration and to bill the user for products and services.

TABLETOPGAMER.COM does not sell your Information or unique identifiers to any third party. The Information gathered is strictly for uses as defined above.

**Links and Affiliate Links:**

This site may contains links to other sites. TABLETOPGAMER.COM is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

This site contains affiliate links to affiliate programs which pay me a commission if you purchase a product or service through that link.  This is one way that this website generates income, so you should be aware that any link on this website may in fact be an affiliate link and I may make money from you clicking on that link and/or purchasing a product or service through that link.

**Security:**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We employ SSL technology in any transmissions of credit card information.

**Choice/Opt-Out:**  Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. Users have options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

**Change/Modify:**  
You may contact us directly regarding changing and modifying information previously provided.

**Cookies:**  
This site may employ temporary cookies to store and retrieve login information through a user’s browser. The cookie allows users to navigate multiple pages with a single login procedure.

**Contacting Us:**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact:

TABLETOPGAMER.com  
c/o Paul Piotrowski  
25855 112th Ave  
Maple Ridge, BC  
Canada V2W1H1
